CRUSADE IN PERU WITH T.B. JOSHUA
PRAYER TIME
God sent forth His Word and healed them all.
It is time to send forth the Word and heal you, deliver you, bless you and set you free.
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Thank You, Lord!
Right now, we'll start from deliverance.
Whatever spirit that is tormenting you,
whatever spirit that has put you in bondage,
whatever spirit that imprisons you,
right now, it is time to release you!
Are you ready?
Are you ready, in the name of Jesus?
Those of you that are sick - are you still on the wheelchair?
Sickness of cancer?
Whatever sickness you are having,
you shall be healed now!
Rise up for prayer!
I want to hear, "Jesus!"
Jesus!
Hallelujah!
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Once again, say, "Jesus, You are welcome to my heart!".
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Jesus, You are welcome to my heart!
Jesus Christ, You are welcome to my heart!
Thank you!
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Ask your neighbour, "Have you received Jesus in your heart?"
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Every knee shall bow!
Every tongue shall confess!
You demon, you familiar spirit,
I command you, in the name of Jesus - out!
I command you out, in the name of Jesus!
You demon, you familiar spirit - I command you in the name of Jesus, out!
Out!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
I say, In the name of Jesus!
Every demon in your life,
wherever you are, wherever you are located,
every demon, every spirit that disturbs your life,
I say, be released!
Be released!
Be set free!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
I release you, in the name of Jesus!
You demon, you familiar spirit,
all power belongs to Jesus!
I say, "You!"
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Thank You, Jesus!
You demon, there is no hiding place.
On the gallery, wherever you are, hear!
Hear!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Hatred.
Fear.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I have hurt her.
I have hurt her sister.
Hatred.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the name of Jesus!
By the mercy of God, you are released.
Begin to release yourself.
Release yourself, by the mercy of God!
I am satan!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Her family hates her.
Her family doesn't love her.
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I am a powerful witch!
How did you destroy her?
I can't.
In the name of Jesus!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Hallelujah!
Right now, those who are sick - whatever sickness or disease,
begin right now to be healed, in Jesus' name.
I command you, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed!
Be released!
In the name of Jesus!
Be healed!
Begin to release yourself, in the name of Jesus!
By the mercy of God, you are released!
By the mercy of God, you are healed, in Jesus' name!
By the mercy of God, you are healed!
By the mercy of God, be healed!
By the mercy of God, be released!
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Healed of Deafness
No Longer Using A Hearing Aid
Say, "By the mercy of God, I am free!"
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Healed of Deafness
No Longer Using A Hearing Aid
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Healed Of Difficulty In Walking
No Longer Using A Walking Aid
Healed of Deafness
No Longer Using A Hearing Aid
Thank You, Jesus!
I had this problem for more than 15 years and had to use this hearing aid.
I prayed to God and came to the crusade.
Thank You! Jesus Christ healed me.
Thank You for sending us Your servant, Prophet T.B. Joshua to bring us the Word of God.
I declare that I am healed by Jesus Christs's stripes!
I am healed by the name of Jesus!
Thank You for sending Your servant, thank You for sending the man of God!
I had been deaf in my ears for over 15 years and God healed me!
I don't need this device anymore!
Over 15 years suffering from deafness!
I had been using a hearing aid but now, God has restored my hearing.
Thank You, Lord Jesus!
Healed of Deafness
No Longer Using A Hearing Aid
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I am the devil.
I am witchcraft.
I am the serpent from the underworld.
What have you done to her?
I am going to destroy her.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Speak out!
How did you destroy her?
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
There are still some sick people.
There are unrepentant demons.
I wil not leave them without them being delivered.
There are some sick people here.
I will not leave you like that.
You must be healed.
You must be delivered.
Healed Of Difficulty In Walking
No Longer Using A Wheelchair
There are some sick people here.
You must be healed before I leave.
In the name of Jesus!
I deliver you, in the name of Jesus!
With all your sicknesses and diseases, you demon, leave my people!
You demon, with all your sicknesses and diseases, with all your infirmity, with all your hardship,
leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
You demon, with all your hardship, with all your pain, with all your infirmity, with all your agony,
with all your depression, with all your sorrow, leave my people!
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Tell your neighbour:
By Your mercy, I am free!
By Your mercy, I am healed!
By Your mercy, I am delivered!
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Healed Of Difficulty In Walking
No Longer Using A Walking Aid
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Healed Of Difficulty In Walking
No Longer Using A Walking Aid
No Longer Using Crutches
Hallelujah!
Glory! Glory!
I am happy.
Unrepentant has repented.
I am happy for you.
Healed Of Difficulty In Walking
No Longer Using A Walking Aid
This is a wonderful atmosphere, an awesome atmosphere -
an atmosphere of miracles, an atmosphere of signs and wonders.
Viewers all over the world,
wherever you are, whatever you are doing at this moment -
are you sleeping, are you awake, are you eating?
Whatever you are doing at this moment, it is not a barrier.
Yes, I am talking to you.
Right now, in the name of Jesus, I release you from all pain, agony, sorrow, affliction.
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in your pain, in your agony - by the mercy of God, you are released!
By the mercy of God, you are released, in the name of Jesus!
Confess your release.
Begin to confess your release.
Right now, are you in abject poverty, affliction, trouble or under oppression?
I say, Confess your release.
I am released, in the name of Jesus!
I am released, by God's mercy!
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Right now, begin to restore yourself.
Glory!
Glory, in my business!
Glory, in my home!
Glory, in my family!
Glory, in my health!
Glory, in my career!
Glory, in my business!
Glory, in my finances!
Glory, in my career!
Glory, in my future!
Glory, in my destiny!
Glory!
Power!
Healed Of Difficulty In Walking
No Longer Using A Walking Aid
I can see you being restored.
I see you healed; I see you being delivered.
I see you cured.
I see you being free.
I see you healed, in Jesus Christ's name.
Rejoice!
Begin to rejoice!
Joy!
Mercy!
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Hallelujah!
I will not leave here without praying for your country.
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Open your lips and begin to pray for your nation.
We have different countries and continents here today.
Open your lips and begin to pray for your country.
Prayer!
Prayer For The Nations At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
God's intervention in your country!
Whatever that is holding your nation back,
God's intervention!
Prayer!
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Open your lips - be it corruption, misappropriation, misrule, misjudgement, idolatry -
begin to release your country, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to release your nation, in the name of Jesus!
Prayer For The Nations At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
In Jesus Christ's name!
I want to lead you in prayer.
Whatever that is holding your nation back - be it corruption, misappropriation, misrule,
be it misjudgement, idolatry, killing, stealing, destruction -
I release your country, in the name of Jesus!
I release your nation, in the name of Jesus!
I release your country - be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be it corruption - be released!
Be it misjudgement, misrule - be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be it idolatry - be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be it the spirit of killing, stealing and destruction - be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Rejoice!
Prayer For The Nations At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Now, coming back to the nation, Peru.
In God's mercy, God has sent me to the nation, Peru.
Whatever that is holding the nation, Peru back, from now, I have released it, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever that is holding the nation, Peru, be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be it corruption - be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be it idolatry - nation, Peru, be released, in the name of Jesus!
Spirit of killing, stealing, destruction, hardship, poverty -
in the name of Jesus, nation, Peru, you are released!
Prayer For The Nations At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Their leaders - cover them with the blood of Jesus!
I want to hear the testimony before the end of this year.
I want to hear freedom from corruption, idolatry, poverty, hardship, in the name of Jesus!
Tell your neighbour, "By God's mercy, the nation, Peru is released!"
By God's mercy, the nation, Peru - be released!
By God's mercy, the nation, Peru has been restored!
Rejoice!
Prayer For The Nations At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Move of mercy in the nation, Peru!
Move of favour in the nation, Peru, in Jesus Christ's name!
Rejoice!
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Hallelujah!
Anywhere you are, we are called to the family of God
by confessing the Lordship of Jesus Christ over our lives.
We are called to the family of God by confessing the Lordship of Jesus Christ over our lives.
Right now, anywhere you are, are you here to rededicate yourself
or you have made Heaven already.
Right now, say after me, Lord Jesus, thank You for Your freedom.
Thank You for saving me today.
Thank You for Your salvation.
Thank You for calling me to Yourself.
Thank You for accepting me.
Thank You for bringing me here today - to a place where I am saved,
I am healed,
I am delivered,
I am set free!
You are my Saviour; thank You for my salvation.
You are my Healer; thank You for my healing.
You are my Redeemer; thank You for my redemption.
Lord, Jesus, thank You!
In Jesus Christ's name!
Mass Prayer At The Peru Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Hallelujah!